[Music]
if somebody accuses me of making fun of
blind people my excuse can't be look you
know my my neck started hurting so I
just started moving it like this you
know and and then you know it just it
just it got kind of bright in there so I
put some shades on and just moving my
neck and then my voice I just started
doing it oh God
Dam oh come on y' I said hey references
to the slave trade would be changed to
the Atlantic triangular trade
come on you guys remember the Atlantic
triangular trade right don't you right
that's when American trapped a surplus
of
triangles and the triangles help build
this nation and in turn receive separate
but equilateral treatment come on it's
like the personification of like uh of
Internet comments it's
like sucks I'm the best it is that's
true that is so
true finally common is running for
president
comments hey America Larry Wilmore here
if you like the nightly show on Comedy
Central like us on Facebook too just
don't poke me I do not like being poked
you can Candy Crush me